In this clip you are going to see how to repair a combination.
Okay we are going to start with repairing a combination break.
With all breaks you always want to start off with drilling in and opening that up so that you can do the repair.
After drilling in, you want to tie into any of the fingers that are going every different way by tapping into it.
Notice how that I am not tapping too hard, just light taps that I loop around that break.
Then the final part of the process is taking the bridge and injecting into the piston with this resin so that we can place this over the break, suction it to the glass and apply our piston to the glass.
Now the piston is the part that is going to most of the work.
After everything has gotten set up, you want to make sure that the sunlight isn't curing it and we are actually in a garage so we will be using an ultraviolet light, a lamp.
What you will do is siphon the air out with a siphon process and go back to injection and you will do this process a couple of times until you have the break completely filled with resin.
At that point, you can either use your lamp, your ultraviolet lamp to cure it, which I will do right now.
Otherwise if you are outside and most repairs can be done outside on nice days, you can just let the sun cure this.